This painting by Paul Cezanne is called “Still Life withApples and Fruit Bowl”
Take a look at the apples in the painting.
Cezanne drew apples that are near the viewer larger
and the apples that were far away smaller.
He used perspective to let the viewers have a sense of distance from the flat picture.
Shall we attach the pictures of apples to a background of Cezanne’s painting
and complete a “Still Life with Apples and Fruit Bowl” that provides perspective?
Prepare a background picture of “Still Life with Apples and Fruit Bowl”
photos of apples, scissors, and glue.
First, cut out apples from photos or magazines.
Big apples,
small apples,
round apples,
and distorted apples.
The more diverse the sizes and shapes of the apples, the better.
Now, place the apples you have cut out on the dishes and the table of the picture.
So that you can have a sense of distance, place the big apples in front,
and the small apples at the back, just like Cezanne’s.
Place big apples in front!
Place small apples at the back!
Like Cezanne-place big apples in front! Small apples at the back!
Create a sense of distance using perspective.
Have you placed the photos of apples on where you wanted to put them?
Attach the photos to the picture.
Well done!